{
    "id": "chukuippa",
    "name": "宙空一派",
    "yomi": "Chukuippa",
    "text": [
        "俺は自宅録音家。今年の夏はあずきバーをそんなに食べませんでした。",
        "I do home recording. I didn't eat many Azuki bar this summer."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "BandCamp",
            "href": "https://chukuippa.bandcamp.com"
        },
        {
            "a": "Twitter",
            "href": "https://www.twitter.com/colorgang/"
        },
        {
            "a": "SoundCloud",
            "href": "https://www.soundcloud.com/colorgang/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Do you have a own motto/policy?",
            "jp": "あなたには座右の銘がありますか？",
            "yes": "Yes i have",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No i haven't",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Which is similar to waht you want?",
            "jp": "座右の銘はどちらに近いですか？",
            "yes": "motto",
            "left": "モットー",
            "no": "policy",
            "right": "ポリシー"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Do you want to exchange your motto/policy?",
            "jp": "座右の銘を交換してみたいと思いますか？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "思う",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "思わない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "What do you think if your motto/policy must be simplicity and fortitude?",
            "jp": "今日からあなたの座右の銘が「質実剛健」になったらどんな気分ですか？",
            "yes": "I think i would be sad",
            "left": "どちらかと言えば悲しい",
            "no": "I think i would be happy",
            "right": "どちらかと言えば嬉しい"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "What do you think if you have to exchange your motto/policy with someone?",
            "jp": "座右の銘（もしくはモットー、ポリシー、考え、信念など）を交換せざるを得ない状況になったら、どう思いますか？",
            "yes": "I would be very excited",
            "left": "ワクワクする",
            "no": "I would be disappointed",
            "right": "テンションが下がる"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Simplicity and fortitude is",
            "jp": "質実剛健って",
            "yes": "difficult",
            "left": "こむずかしい",
            "no": "cool",
            "right": "かっこいい"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "A Three years on a stone three years for me is",
            "jp": "石の上にも三年は",
            "yes": "long",
            "left": "長い",
            "no": "short",
            "right": "短い"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Good fortune and happiness will come to the home of those who smile",
            "jp": "笑う門には福来たる",
            "yes": "Yes i think so too",
            "left": "に違いない",
            "no": "Not so much...",
            "right": "とは限らない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "You would choose",
            "jp": "もし選ぶなら、",
            "yes": "Continuity is the father of success",
            "left": "継続は力なり",
            "no": "Sometimes you just have to give up",
            "right": "辞め時が肝心"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "You would choose",
            "jp": "もし選ぶなら、",
            "yes": "Strike while the iron is hot",
            "left": "善は急げ",
            "no": "More haste, less speed",
            "right": "急がば回れ"
        }
    ]
}